module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who wrote the novel Jurassic Park?', 
      a: 'John Grisham', 
      b: 'Michael Chrichton',
      c: 'JK Rowling',
      d: 'Ian Malcom',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Before Chrichton even published the book, Universal Pictures paid him _____ for the rights.', 
      a: '$2 million', 
      b: '$3 million',
      c: '$450000',
      d: '$750000',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many minutes do dinosaurs appear on screen in the movie?', 
      a: '60', 
      b: '30',
      c: '15',
      d: '5',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What color is the jello in Lex\'s spoon when her hand starts shaking?', 
      a: 'Red', 
      b: 'Green',
      c: 'Blue',
      d: 'Rainbow',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What actual sound was used for the T Rex\'s footsteps?', 
      a: 'Large bass drum hits', 
      b: 'A guy going GOOOSZH',
      c: 'Explosive devices going off',
      d: 'Cut sequoias crashing to the ground',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year was the movie released?', 
      a: '1990', 
      b: '1991',
      c: '1992',
      d: '1993',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who played Alan Grant?', 
      a: 'Sam Neill', 
      b: 'Sam Smith',
      c: 'Neill Patrick Harris',
      d: 'Harrison Ford',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'On which Hawaiian island was much of the film shot?', 
      a: 'Hawaii', 
      b: 'Kauai',
      c: 'Maui',
      d: 'Oahu',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Jurassic Park was the 2nd highest grossing film of the 20th century behind what film?', 
      a: 'E.T.', 
      b: 'The Godfather',
      c: 'Titanic',
      d: 'Schindlers List',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'John Hammond was played by the brother of what famous BBC narrator?', 
      a: 'Richard Attenborough', 
      b: 'John Attenborough',
      c: 'David Attenborough',
      d: 'Frederick Attenborough',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};